Jayne McELHENY

Creative Director

Conshohocken, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jayne-McELHENY/047037f390b4bbc5

Passionate visual designer with strong management, artistic and design background, as well as technical, organizational and interpersonal skills. With over 27 years experience, I am always seeking out new challenges and other learning opportunities with enthusiasm to continue to inspire others, and work hard to develop and grow as a creative leader.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Director

SunGard Data Systems - Wayne, PA - 2007 to 2014

Corporate in-house design manager and graphic designer at a fast-paced, global software technology company, responsible for providing creative leadership and direction, concept development and graphic design for print and web applications that are compelling, creative and on-brand.

Art Director

Miller Designworks - Phoenixville, PA - 2005 to 2007

Worked within a studio environment on a variety of different types of projects to successfully execute all aspects of project management from proposal through final delivery for a diverse group of clients including; SunGard Data Systems, CertainTeed Corporation, TruMark Financial Credit Union, BDP International and Johnson & Johnson.

Creative Director

Orthovita Incorporated - Malvern, PA - 1997 to 2005

Corporate in-house design manager and graphic designer for an international, FDA regulated medical device company. Developed all processes and procedures for it's new in-house creative services department, as well as establishing new product logos and brand guidelines to tell the company's story with a distincitive personality and cutting-edge tone.

Freelance Designer

JK Design - Conshohocken, PA - 1989 to 1997

Directed and supervised overall creative and business activities for a diverse group of clients. Managed suppliers (photographers, illustrators, copywriters and printers), defined and interpreted client marketing objectives and expectations to implement compelling graphic design solutions for a multitude of deliverables, specializing in logo design and corporate identity programs.

Customer Service Representative

Airborne Express - King of Prussia, PA - 1987 to 1996

Responsibilities included data entry, answering phones, accounts payable and receivables, ordered office supplies, filing, entering payroll, resolving attempted deliveries (bad addresses, signature required packages, etc.), driver dispatch, as well as working with with airlines and couriers to arrange same day deliveries.

Senior Graphic Designer

Randee Berman Design - Philadelphia, PA - 1986 to 1989

Started as a Junior Designer 6 months prior to earning my degree. Worked my way up to Senior Designer within 2 years. Significant achievement was independently designing the brand identity for Italian Bistro Restaurants; a local chain of 5 restaurants in the tri-state area.

AWARDS

EDUCATION

BFA in Graphic Design

University of the Arts - Philadelphia, PA 1987

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite 6 (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator), MS Office (Outlook, Office, Excel, PowerPoint), Apple iWork (Keynote, Pages, Numbers), QuarkXpress

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Please see LinkedIn for more details including recommendations and endorsements. Portfolio available upon request.

[...]